Exercise 1-38, intonation shifts. Practice the following intonation shifts. Accident,
accidental, accidentally, president, presidential, presidentially, develop,
development, developmental, developmentally, quantity, quantify,
quantification. maximum, maximize, maximization, origin, original, originate,
origination, analyze, analysis, analytic, catalyze, catalysis, catalytic, real,
realize, reality, realization, condemn, condemnatory,
condemnation, revolve, revolver, revolutionary, create, creative, creation,
creativity. This is a key word stress issue for Indians who tend to stress the
first syllable develop instead of the second develop. This is the same situation
in component and beginning.